subdreamer.com 2016-03-14

# Privacy Policy - CMS for Everyone - Subdreamer

Thank you for visiting our web site. This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.

Please note that this Privacy Policy applies to all Subdreamer Web Development websites: subdreamer.com, subdreamer.org and softwaredroid.com

If you follow a link from our sites to external/other web sites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.

 **Collection of Information**  
We collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. The information you provide is used to fulfill your specific request such as processing orders or support requests.

 **Cookie/Tracking Technology**  
The Site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors or allow persistent logins. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.

 **Mailing Lists**  
As a member of our Web site you may occasionally receive an email newsletter informing you of new products and services. You may choose not to receive further email messages by clicking the “unsubscribe” link or instructions at the bottom of the email or using your user control panel on the relevant website to opt-out. Additionally, as a customer of Subdreamer CMS you may occasionally receive an email informing you of new products and services, product updates, important notices or other information relevant to your licensed software. You may choose not to receive further email messages by clicking the “unsubscribe” link or instructions at the bottom of the email. We recommend you always receive customer related emails to ensure you don't miss sale offers relevant to the products you use and important security or other updates.

 **Distribution of Information**  
We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes.

 **Commitment to Data Security**  
Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings.

 **Privacy Contact Information**  
If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us any time.

We reserve the right to make changes to this policy.
